I'm sorry that your Guru isn't honest
and now that everyone's eyes are open
he'll have to stop soon so one little
mistake one little mistake and he got
caught bro is Alex calling trades live
yes is he flipping $100 into a million
no he blew the account long ago the
challenge won't go far he thrives on
Deception right now the evidence stacked
against you just doesn't look good good
morning ladies and gentlemen as much as
I would want to go right into the
markets and show you my trades on this
week where I'm going to be earning the
$90,000 into 200 I have to spoon feed my
children my very special unique children
the haters come here come here
[Music]
airplane so as you guys know there has
been an eight-part YouTube series where
I've been turning $100 to $90,000 right
now and there has been zero hate nobody
has said absolutely anything but now
finally the challenge is becoming big
we're turning up big numbers so
everything we've done to this point is
absolutely legit but nobody has hated
because of two reasons one everything is
legit and two the thumbnail isn't that
attractive oh Alex turned $100 into 200
it's fake ah no one cares about 200
bucks oh Alex faked the 200 into 10,000
ah it's fake oh but now Alex faked the
whole entire thing now you got a video
and thank you thank you very much Round
of Applause please Round of Applause
ladies and gentlemen thank you very much
cuz now you just made me look so much
more legit and I'm going to to now
attack all of your argument points
because you have now infected the mind
of the other 2% of the people that were
skeptical you're never going to infect
the 96% of the people that have been
following the challenge and know
everything is legit so I'm sorry for
those 98% of you guys that have been
watching the series and are educated
that I have to now waste 5 minutes of
this video educating the 2% of re I
can't use that word I want to say
special people first one why don't you
show the trade history
why don't you huh I don't why don't you
I know I know thought you were my Guru I
know I know I know I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm sorry I had to pay my car bills I
had to I had to [__] they got
me what this is the stupidest one ever
all right as you guys can see right here
I show the trade history once twice
three times four times five times six
times go do your research that I am
literally showing the trade history in
the whole entire challenge it's not my
fault you want to be lazy and not go and
watch these videos because they're too
long I know you're special your
attention span is low and you can't go
watch an hour long video I'm sorry go go
to the doctor and ask them for ader roll
it it helps it might help you or
meditate or do something don't call me a
scav cuz you don't want to go through
your own research which ties into the
next point which is going to be why
don't you show the withdraw with no
traits so I'm going to tie both of these
together right now so their alleged
argument is that this screenshot is fake
I [__] up your Guru made a mistake
while lying to you what a [__] title
huh 100 to the mill is a SK at M Alex
lied to everyone at least you didn't
call you scammer I know at least he
didn't call him a scammer he's call me a
SC ATM thank you buddy dude thanks man
thank you bro well now you look like a
re I can't use that word now you look
special because I'm about to literally
eat be you up so their whole argument is
that I [__] up in the telegram I
uploaded this screenshot right here on
August 25th and I posted a screenshot
where on the monthly time frame I show
the withdraw and there's no trade
history and that's it they say the whole
entire challenge is fake because of this
like if I don't have a whole entire
eight-part YouTube series video of me
showing the before the during the after
of every single one of my traits their
whole argument is that I [__] up and I
showed the month and on the day as well
and there's no trade history well let's
get to the bottom of it so let's go
right into it first things first is
going to be the challenge and the
history so let's go right into our
trusty platform my effects book we're
going to go right into the my effect
book which by the way we have clearly
shown multiple times throughout the
whole entire challenge it's not like I'm
showing this you right now for the first
time which is what you guys would
probably claim you guys can see right
here how I started the challenge with a
100 $1 now let's go to the trades
there's no trades the orders there's no
orders the history oh drum roll please
drum roll please all right so we are now
here on the new edited fake
history you guys can clearly see how I
took
$100 up until
$22,000 add all this up do the math you
special people and you guys can see
right here the withdraw their alleged
claim is that this screenshot is showing
people that I withdrew fake money from a
different account and that this is not
real buddy what time does that say
18482 okay I click here
18482 what does it say right here 8 oh
[__]
822 how do we do that how do we fake
that how do we do that cuz it's not fake
it's real why is there a screen shot
though right which is so first of all
let's go straight into the first point
which is why don't you show the trade
history well clearly that right there is
busted check that off and we'll just go
right into the current account that
we're in right now and then we'll show
the trade history where we started off
with $20,000 and then we took it up to
$70,000 with these two trades if you
haven't seen those trades make sure you
go watch the last YouTube video that we
just did thanks and you guys can see how
it's all legit and then the next one is
why does the withdraw show 1 month and
no traits now this is the one where I
actually don't have the [__] answer
to I would love to have the answer to it
but I don't know why and I think I know
what went wrong so let me show you an
example so let's come here now to the
metat trator 4 metat trator 5 right so
whenever you log into metat Trader you
can see how this bottom right thing
right here is loading probably what I
did is I had the history tab on the
month or the day on metat trator 4 and
when I opened the app it was loading and
it was refreshing and I just happened to
screenshot it at that very moment and it
popped up with the month and then it
went back to the DAT I don't have the
reason why this is like this and I would
love to go to medat trador 4 and show
you guys that actual history of the
month and the week and the day but the
broker that I was using which you guys
can see right here that it is a real
account is disconnected they no longer
have this server and I simply cannot go
back and watch the history I would
literally love to trust me
but thankfully luckily literally luckily
thank Lord Jes literally no no for real
cuz if not I would literally have no
explanation from this the whole entire
Challenge on that metatrader account I
had connected to the my effect book go
look at the videos do your research look
you guys can see right here literally
the whole entire challenge I had on my
history and luckily this right here is
as well as right here you guys can see
how the last update was on 8 22 they
lost their license on 822 the same day
that I have the withdraw withdraw is on
822 so this is literally going to answer
both questions why don't you show the
trade history clearly I do why does the
widraw show one month with no trades I
literally don't have the answer to this
but this is their whole point of
argument they said that I posted a
screenshot on telegram oh which by the
way if you're not in the telegram right
now join like there's 169,000 Traders
and over 100,000 people see every single
one of the trades that I am sending in
real time on this 100 to the mill series
you guys are watching these trades late
join the telegram and you can see the
trades before anybody else say I'm
literally sending signals in this free
telegram please go join and if you join
you might see me [__] up again but this
is literally the whole point of argument
that the challenge is fake and that it
blew the account because of this buddy
it is literally mathematically
impossible for me to blow the challenge
based off of the trades that have I have
been taking it's literally impossible
question one or concern one or hate one
busted why does a withdraw show one
month in no trades busted now second why
complain about the fees when you
allegedly make 300K a
day [__] did
I is that even spelled right alleged
alleged hey Siri uhhuh how do you spell
allegedly a l l e g e d l y had to fix
it bu had to fix that if now they say oh
no the guy I don't know a
literate all right so why do you
complain about the fees when you legally
make $300,000 a day I did not complain
about the fees buddies I complained
about the slippage once again go do your
due diligence I complained about the
slippage on the account and the broker
that I used to make 300K a day on was a
very long time ago and they lost their
man Trader 4 met Trader 5 license as
well and they came out with this new web
server and they came out with this new
platform that I didn't like so I
transferred to a new broker why oh cuz
why don't you use the broker that you
used before when you were making 300K
and cuz I don't [__] want to cuz they
have a different platform and I don't
like it I moved to a new one now and
this new one that I have now I don't
like it either and I'm currently
transferring through and then this leads
me to the next Point why which is
follows up with this one why don't you
share the link for the broker oh my God
how many times do I have to say this I
don't promote a broker if I was somebody
else if I was any these haters trust me
they would have taken the deal I
literally got offered two weeks ago
$600,000 a month to promote a broker in
order to show people where I'm taking
the challenge dude look how many of you
guys are watching these videos over
100,000 of you guys within the two weeks
imagine I put an affiliate link all
100,000 of you guys will go to that
broker you know how much money I will
make the broker and how much money I
will make a lot more than this challenge
I'll tell you that for sure and I'm not
doing it to be transparent and show you
guys that I make only money from Trad
trading yeah do I have a info product
where I teach people how to trade [__]
yeah I'm literally turning people into a
profitable Trader where they're having
their own 100 to the mill series you can
see these students right here how they
have literally taken the same trades as
me in the hundreds of the mill series
and even made more money than me all I
had do is trade and teach people how to
do the same thing I don't want broker
affiliation I don't want any of this
stuff as of right now and I don't share
the link or don't show the broker for
you guys to show you guys how legit and
how transparent I am and I guarantee you
none of these haters can say the same
thing and they would never in my
position first all they can't afford to
be in my position respectfully
and and they would not do the same thing
so I wanted to clear up all these things
oh I mean d so once again the whole
point of this thing is show the history
show the history
show okay is that it is that really like
ask for something else come on show like
ask for my Social Security there I'll be
like [__] you know history clearly myth
busted myth busted wait is this busted
or is this plausible or a myth starting
to look like a myth myth right whatever
all right so here we clearly have the
history on the hundreds of mil to this
point then we have the current history
you see how it's loading it's probably
where I took the screenshot and it got
uploaded this is currently right now
where we are where we took 20,000 to
70,000 and we're now going to take this
week 90,000 to
278,000 and for any of you guys out
there that again want to have concerns
with the challenge bro like dude you
guys don't understand how much I take
care of my reputation and you guys can
see how there's more love than any hate
dude look how many people watch me on a
daily basis don't you think something
would have popped up a long time ago
this is my Instagram right who's this
guy right here huh huh huh what you know
about that son as you guys can see there
is well over 130,000 people that watch
my stories every single day I'm not
going to let some little hater or some
little wannabe want to take something
out of proportion just for views because
it's going to benefit their Channel and
they're going to be able to make $50
more more this month because is a
monetization sorry can't have let that
happen because I'm literally showing you
guys this as transparent and as legit as
it gets and little tip of advice to the
people out there that are or the 2% of
people that are in that audience you
never want to have an audience build off
of hate that's not how you build the
community trust me you want to build an
audience off of showing back giving love
and providing value not taking things
out of context just so you get views
because the person that you're talking
about is bigger and just once again if
this isn't enough I'm not about to spend
the whole entire this series on this
right here go watch the 100 to the mill
series watch the before the during the
after of these eight videos and then
come back to me and have something to
say until then so now that we have
broken down and discussed every single
one of these topics and clearly shown
you guys that everything is legit let's
get into the markets and have the actual
trade update we're going to be
pause was
this oh
I knew it the cars are rented [__] [__]
[__] they're not going to have anything
to say with this or like you know what
the whole challenge to the mill series
is legit but he blew the account now I
attack that point the challenge of the M
series is legit he didn't blow accounts
but his cars are
rented all right y make sure to hide the
car rental company stuff all right you
got it all right so we're here in the
Bugatti
let's just show my God like like if this
information is not enough like if this
information is not enough anybody can do
that anybody anybody can fake that it's
myam
right but can you fake
this are are you ready you ready to edit
you you can fake it now okay how can you
fake
this registration to what company the
one and only set and forgets LLC
no no no but then the other cars are
fake this is a ticket this car doesn't
even have a
registration [__] see we caught him it
doesn't say fxlg on
it oh wait think you you added another
crack onto that should I just break it
right
now ready
I wa but the G wagon's fake how can
Alice get in his hands on one to 25 in
the world G wagon it's impossible dude
it has to be fake one and only swing
trading lab
LLC haters please try again I don't want
to oh no the be's
fake yeah you know what the beo is fake
yeah it's fake so with that being said
oh no oh no the house is fake oh we got
him he rent something all right bro I'm
done with this [__] let's go back now to
do real trade updates and by the way
this is my first ever response to a
hater first and final response I just
wanted to do it because I'm doing
something legendary and don't want to
have one small misconception this big
get taking out of context for somebody
else when I get views so first and final
response never doing it ever again I get
it you guys wanted attention you got it
but now you look I want to use the word
but I can't now you look unique and
special and you just verified me and my
challenge a lot more with that being
said let's get into it TR
for this week so we're going to start
off the 100 to the mill Series this week
with a starting balance of
$90,000 as you guys can see right here
and this
$90,000 is now going to be where we're
trying to take the $200,000 First Market
we were interested in is
gbpusd so we were waiting for a retest
of this level of support and resistance
and then sell but that has already
happened basically missed this trade
because we weren't interested in taking
the trade at London session on Sunday
GBP nzd is market number two we're
waiting for a higher low retest of this
level with retest structure EMA and
round psychological level in order for
us to take this trade to the upside
looks like it already had the push to
the upside that we wanted to without
having the retest so we got to be on the
lookout to see if it does come back here
how it will look if we will be
interested in taking this trade then we
have
audusd which has a beautiful one of the
most beautiful left head right shoulders
that I've seen in quite some time and
we're going to now wait for a retest of
this neckline of the head and shoulders
in order to take this position to the
downside it's already kind of having
that break and retest and that sell but
that's not quite what I'd want I want to
have more of a actual retest and
rejection from this point right here
just going to make it look a lot cleaner
USD JPY so this is the trade that we
took last week once again bro it's funny
cuz I I just love doing this uh we took
this sell on USD JPY as you guys can see
right here we have 9004 904 where you
close out the position right here is
where we made the money from this point
to this point look at the market price
and now this week we are looking to now
enter a new added position on this
potentially so as you guys can see this
is here a very strong level of support
support support resistance and support
we're now going to be waiting for a
retest rejection from this round
psychological level 144,000 to then
enter the cell to the downside looks
like it Wicked into that area right now
but too fast we got to wait for a better
retest GBP JPY we were anticipating for
price to have a retest of this level of
support and resistance in order for us
to then sell which we're still on our
way there and waiting for that we have
Euro AUD which we're waiting for a
retest of this left head potential right
shoulder which going to have a retest of
this very strong level of support and
resistance and a retest of the EMA to
then head to the upside so we're just
anticipating that pullback right now
being very patient with it because I
like this trade a lot then we have nzd
CAD which has had the break exactly how
I wanted to having the break now
confirming the left head right shoulder
we broken through the neckline we got to
wait for this Candlestick to close the
key word have to wait it's not a
confirmation of The Head and Shoulders
this Candlestick still has about 6 hours
in it in order for it to actually move
so this can have a ginormous Wick and
then heading to the upside if in 6 hours
it doesn't close how we wanted to so we
have to wait for that as you can see on
the 4 Hour we are clearly having a very
cleaner Head and Shoulders we're now
going to retest and head to the downside
but key word have to wait for this daily
time frame Candlestick to close it's not
going to go up to my number one pair for
the week next we have GBP CAD which we
were looking for a break and retest to
them bu which is not happening and then
USD CHF not even interested in it so
quite some markets this week uh what
update just to go kind of everything is
unfolding very fast now it's the
beginning of the week let's see where
this week can now takes us so if you
guys had any concerns or the whole hate
stuff is now cleared up please let me
know in the comments I read a lot of
your guys' comments and it helps me out
let me know that you guys are enjoying
what I'm doing and that it's actually
helping and changing your guys' lives
and you guys giving me that feedback
means everything I'm putting in all the
time in love to you guys you guys can
get better into trading and you guys can
hopefully potentially one day be like me
which I definitely think if you show up
every single day and you do what you got
to do I think it's very possible I don't
have any special skill I don't have any
you know aeroterrestrial
uh add-on like the only thing is I'm 68
it's the only thing if you're not 68
your odds are succeeding are a little
bit harder but you know it's okay so but
that being said said and forget and
we'll update you in a
bit but there's one question they still
haven't answered
demo trador what do you mean dude is the
new account a demo account or Live
account you didn't show
that hey you think you you think you can
run demo trator can't
hide here we go again the
[Music]
airplane what is this guy what is this
guy's name the guy that goes
kab kab he goes by he goes simply
by one interesting man he goes
by I'm let you eat in peace for
now quick trade update right now is
going on we're going to go look at a new
house right now we're still on the house
tour mission so pick of the legend okay
hey what's up guys you want to know what
we started off the video saying like we
started exposing how the trades are
fake oh really yeah so can I see your
Live account no can I can can I see your
Live account on your
traes all right so give me
that that's a nice demo count is that is
that demo sir no how do we know show us
Liars oh
[Music]
[__] all right so who has a better
physique between him and I so he's got a
little bit more chest development right
you you have a little bit you actually
have a lot of potential you have more of
a a bigger back and a big so that's why
you have a if when you lean out you'll
have a really good V taper but he's a
little bit leaner right now and has
better chest back let me see the
back no but don't don't scrunch it up
you got to open it up you need help POS
it he knows how to pose better I'll be
honest okay so it's a it's it's it's a I
don't want to say it's a tie it depends
what you're looking for okay you can
rest we can rest we can rest you have
more potential because of your structure
you have a bigger back right you are a
little bit leaner so you can see the
cuts a little better but you will have a
better physique right now it's a
different look that's hard to
say right who has better
eyes you do
[Music]
you all right ladies and gentlemen we
are back in the office today was
actually an interesting day we hit the
gym went to go see a new house that's it
I did grocery shopping oh y s the
grocery sh thanks bro but with that
being said trade update it is currently
11: in the afternoon Monday evening the
account is currently exactly the same at
$90,000 you guys are wondering why is my
hand scratched up it's because I have a
cat and I occasionally decid to into a
fight with it and it's for of the fence
is to bite scratch and that's the
outcome of it so yeah right now trade
update $90,000 no trade so let's look at
the market so my new favorite Market is
by far going to be
nzdcad nzdcad has closed exactly how I
wanted on The Daily time frame with the
very strong daily body Candlestick
closure under we now we're going to be
waiting for a little pullback to then
sell we can see here on the 4 Hour that
we kind of did have that kind of a
little ugly pullback but didn't make it
quite all the way to even area of
Interest one or area of Interest number
two so we're going to wait for this pull
back to then sell
gbpusd we had to push to the downside
how we anticipated the only way I can
enter this trade is that we have a deer
pull back to and cell technically the
trade has already played out so missed
this trade gbpnzd same exact thing it
had the push without having to retested
the area that we wanted it to
technically missed this trade audusd
currently daily retesting the neckline
not how I wanted to I want a little bit
of a deeper pullback so of right now
this trade is not in my interest at all
USD JPY in the other hand is having a
solid pull back into this level of
support supports and now potentially
going to be used as resistance we're
going to be waiting for the rejection of
this EMA and this structure level and
round psychological 14400 to then head
to the downside so I'm going to set my
alarm right at the top of this area
right here and as you guys can see this
is already working its way up from where
we started at the beginning of the week
so I'm going to put this pair to the top
so now we have nzd CAD as number one USD
JPY as number two next Market is GBP JPY
we have had now the pullback Candlestick
which is currently forming but as of
right now it's still waiting for the
pull back on it it's going to be my
number third pair for the week so we
take it from this spot we bump it up and
now on audusd we already covered it Euro
AUD we are still waiting for this
pullback of this area to then buy just
waiting on that and last but not least
GBP CAD we were waiting for a r to set
and buy not happening so our main focus
is going to be GJ pullback for sales UJ
pullback for sales and nzdcad pullback
for
sales that being
said we're going to Now set forget good
morning ladies and gentlemen it's it is
currently 9:44 in the morning Tuesday
morning so last night fell as sleep
around 2: in the morning another usual
night and we're back this morning with
some interesting markets to trade so let
me show you guys so nzd CAD exactly how
I explained it yesterday we were
anticipating for price to have the
retest of this area and that is exactly
what is happening right now when you go
down to the lower time frames you can
very clearly see that we are officially
having our first clean rejection from
this level of support and resistance and
now when we go down to the 1 hour we can
see that the 1 hour is creating indeed a
potential shift of structure move even
though indeed yes this is the lower high
this is the lower low this is the shift
of structure within the move let's check
out the 30 minute time frame you can see
the 30 minute time frame is doing the
exact same thing in order for me to
execute and enter this position I have
to wait for a body Candlestick closure
under this structure level right here
soon as we get that then I'm going to be
waiting for a little quick retest so we
can take this trade to the downside or
just a little quick engulfing on this
position to then enter this trade I
really really really like this trade
does give me very clean cells to have a
nice stop loss right around for 20 Pips
and then my first take profit on this
position as crazy as this my sound could
even be this structure point right here
I don't think it's going to make it to
that level today cuz I I I think I don't
think this one weekly Candlestick could
make it that far I think within 2 weeks
so maybe the take profit for this week
could be the next even the next 4-Hour
structure level is still all the way
down there so maybe we can bump it up a
little bit to this level of support and
resistance right here for a quick one
two three risk reward so stay tuned for
that USD JPY on the other hand hasn't
quite made it to the area of Interest
how I wanted it to it's crazy because
the alarm that I put yesterday at 143.5
41 has did not even hit look at that
Wick barely made it up to that point
right there like it was literally one
pip away but we didn't make it not that
I would have sold it would have hit that
alarm but it would have notified me that
it's getting closer to the area of
Interest we got to wait for this trade
to make it to the area of interest to be
interested in taking this position right
now this position at this point we would
have loved for this Wick to look
something like that that would have been
a confirmed rejection of the area of
interest but since we have not made it
we don't have that confirmation and not
interested in taking this TR trade just
yet still waiting for the retest of this
area so I can enter the trade to the
downside next is GBP nzd looks like it
is having the pullback indeed to retest
the EMA retest the structure level
retest round psychological level and it
looks very clean on The Daily time frame
love how it looks I believe that this
can to have one red Candlestick here and
then the next day could have the push so
it could be like a trade maybe for
Thursday and the 4 Hour looks a little
bit weird because now this is the higher
high and now we're bearish but it might
have to go bearish with the daily to
have the pullback and we have to see how
it reacts once it gets to this point I'm
going to put an alarm right around this
area here so it can notify me once price
gets there at
21218 GBP JPY still waiting on the
retest of this level in order to be able
to be interested in sells and gpusd not
even interested in it it's gone so our
main focus is on USD JPY to retest for
sale nzdcad is borderline about to to
enter so we're actively just waiting on
this position to have the break and yeah
that's trade up there right now accounts
as you guys can see currently in the
morning it is sitting at
$90,000 same exact amount so we'll
update you guys as the day goes all
right guys trade update it is currently
10:04 p.m. so literally today we've done
nothing it's been raining all day
literally I've been home all day doing
nothing so right now currently we have
been anticipating for price to have a
sell from the bottom of
gbpnzd CAD what nzd CAD yes and nzd CAD
we were waiting for our breaking ret
from this area here and currently right
now we are reacting from this area which
is it is indeed where I'm looking to
enter the trade but I would just love if
it were to break and retest under this
structure level here it would just look
a lot cleaner if price were to have this
so then we can sell daily time frame we
ended up closing off with a solid daily
bullish pullback Candlestick stayed
under the structure level which is great
now we can anticipate this Candlestick
to then head to the downside it's not
going to be a bad trade I can't even lie
even if we were to execute it literally
right now like if we execute this trade
at this very Point have our stop loss
right above this area for about we could
we could even make it 20 Pips and our
first take profet would be here still a
solid 1 to four but you know what I
rather wait for a little extra push
confirmation then we can bring down our
stock stop loss and then we get the same
one to four like you don't have to enter
the trade right at the top point and
have this like this you can wait for a
better confirmation that price has had
to move and then you just lower your
stop loss a little bit and you get the
same risk to reward ratio literally
nothing [__] changes so for now I'm
going to be waiting on this to give me a
confirmation rejection from this area
like another engulfing Candlestick or a
solid break and retest to the downside
next
usdjpy this trade but imagine we would
still been holding this position from
over here all the way to this point a 1
to 11 risk to 1 to 10.5 risk to reward
that'd be insane but price never pulled
back to the area how he wanted to in
order to enter the sell so the cell just
kept going so this trade was another one
that we have missed next we have
gbpnzd which we are waiting for price to
retest this area to then buy price has
not made it there so there's nothing
that we do then we have GBP JPY which we
were waiting for price to retest this
area to sell hasn't and gbpusd same
exact thing breth this a sell it hasn't
happened so it looks like right now our
only solid trade opportunity that we
have is literally just nzd CAD for sales
so we're going to very much be on the
lookout for this I'm going to put my
alarm right under this 1H hour bullish
engulfing Candlestick structure point
which is going to be right around here
so we have an alarm set up at 0.83
603 so we're going to do now is been a
boring day it's been raining we're going
to go do a campfire I'm feeling some
s'mores and uh I don't know just want to
go out on the G wagon do a campfire see
if we [__] get attacked by a Jaguar
I'm going to take
my I what should we go shoot this
[__] we never shot it before yeah we've
never shot I don't know you didn't even
know if he
shoots you think it's safe to shoot
this why not cuz I dude I don't know bro
imagine you shoot it boom and blows up
your hand imagine I lose my dude that
would suck we I need this I only need
one think about it to to place a trade
yeah exactly but N I think we should
play
Same we're just [__] take one of
these
Johns you know about
that America America
[Applause]
[Music]
you know a lot of people can look at me
today and be like you know what he got
lucky it was easy for
him what people don't see is those
endless nights of dark dark dark times
of losing money every single day without
knowing if I was going to succeed and
the money the cars the Jets the watches
all it's [__] [__] the skill set
that I learned by myself in that dark
room every single night showing up when
things were bad when things got a little
bit good and then bad again is what got
me those things and you can take all
those things away from me right now and
the skill set that I've acquired will
bring it right back it's not about the
materialistic things that I have it's
the knowledge and the experience that
I've acquired over time that got me to
the position that I am today and nobody
could take that [__] [__] away from
me you give me my money
trade update ladies and gentlemen from
R please ladies and gentlemen it is
currently
11:15 in the morning and as of right now
the account is currently sitting at a
whopping you blew the account again it's
like
$15,000 now you know what let me just
we're currently sitting at
$115,000 now the reason why I'm not
excited is because we could have
literally been in this much profit we've
been holding the last trade but sucks so
we had to overexpose ourselves but it's
okay why because the strategy is working
once again nzdcad literally having left
head right shoulder retest of the
neckline exactly what I explained on the
1 hour time frame higher high higher low
higher high once it breaks and retests
this neckline we will be interested in
selling and boys that is exactly what we
did we broke and we retested once again
like does not get any more legit than
this oh but you want to know what's the
crazy part that the downside potential
of this trade is massive we can reach
lows of all the way up to this structure
point right here but we're not going to
do that we're not going to be greedy
we're going to be realistic and set real
take profits and we enter this position
once we body close under this right here
we're pretty much good but you want to
know what's the crazy part I'm not the
only one that entered this trade sadly
you guys are watching this after it
already happened so you're probably
wondering [__] how can I make those
trades as well it's very simple this
exact same entry I
well this exact same entry earlier this
morning so right now it's 11:17 in the
morning at 10: in the morning so about
an hour and a half ago I asked if you're
an nzdcad at everyone put a thumbs up in
the message above and then post your
entries 177 people confirmed that they
entered this position and you can just
scroll down here this is my private
swing trading lab Community you can see
all these people entering the same
positions and adding their confluences
you can see this guy right here adding
all his entries like literally every
single person showing the trade that
they have ented this guy took 2,000 to
3,000 look at this right let's just pass
by 100 different people that have legit
entered the same position let's forget
that this guy just turned 90 bucks into
150 not a big deal right this guy see I
I like these right this guy's using risk
management this guy's being responsible
but there's one guy down here hold on
let me find him where is he all right
look let me see um one second one second
where where is this guy it this guy no
this guy's up like 10 grand
one second where is this guy we have to
go through is it this guy this oh no not
this guy but it's just like this guy 90
bucks to 230 love it phenomenal is it
this guy 100 bucks to 300 no it's not
this guy where is he where is this dude
come on this guy took like $5 to 200 I'm
totally kidding dude these are all
students just posting their entries bro
one second where is it where is it where
it right here here he is oh no wrong guy
this guy $80 to
$240 on the same nzd CAD CS then we have
this guy that he took the AUD usds he
made 500 this guy made 4.7k and I just
told the students right now like bro
thank you to every single one of you
guys that took the nzd cad it confirms
that my teachings are working and in
fact you don't need trade signals to
succeed all you need is the skill set
and that motivates me to keep teaching
cuz I get on a call every single week
with my students and I try and literally
pour out as much wisdom and knowledge as
I possibly can on those one or two hours
that I do with them and it just confirms
you don't need signals you just need the
skill set once you get the skill set the
money will come so as of right now GBP
no nzdcad is having a very clean
momentum to the downside just waiting
for Body candles to close around the
here for to continue to hold the trade
and it's going to be great and gbpnzd
never retested so we never enter the
trade USD JPY never retested so we never
entered the trade so so far only one
trade is needed nzdcad and I am I'm
liking this price action so far I like
how we did body Candlestick closure
under that structure level now we can
create a lower high and then a lower low
so trade update we are up
$117,000 all right what is going on guys
trade update so right now it is
currently 2:25 in the morning so I
haven't done an update since earlier
today today we pretty much just I don't
even know I can't fall asleep right now
it's 2:22 in the morning I'm literally
looking at the markets like this right
now so what I'm going to do is I'm going
to go take a shower and I'm going to be
watching every single tick because I
cannot let this account below trade
update we are now currently down $3,000
on the challenge so
earlier there it is so earlier we were
obviously up about $30,000 but we
decided to set and forget as we should
and now the trade is simply reversing
back into the area where I expected it
to pull back obviously you just never
want that to happen but let me explain
so you guys can see that we are about
down about
$3,000 and uh here in the markets daily
time frame has had a very solid push to
the downside very strong daily bearish
and go from Candlestick but looks like
the 4H hour after creating this new
lower low in order for us to continue
heading to the downside we have to
create a lower high now this it's at the
point where it could have the reaction
from the support support support level
to then actually sell which is actually
great but it could actually make it all
the way back up and retest uh and create
a double top at this area which I don't
think it will make it but I do think
that it could head to the downside from
this point right here you can also see
it looks like it's creating another Head
and Shoulders on the 1 hour time frame
so we had a little head and shoulders to
enter at this point right here left head
right shoulder and now it looks like
we're getting another left head right
shoulder this is literally at the area
where it's supposed to have the push to
the downside not looking to add any
entries just simply looking to set and
forget this position and see where this
trade takes us I'm going to be watching
every single tick to see if it decides
to break
above um I don't know like if it breaks
above this structure level right here I
will probably be closing the position
just because I think it could go all the
way up into stop loss so I'll be
updating you guys USD JPY never pulled
back so we simply are waiting for that
there GBP nzd pulled back to the area of
interest but you guys have to keep in
mind it is Thursday so not sure if I
want to get into this position quite
just yet but it did pull back so we are
keeping our eye on it and then every
single other Market we're just not quite
interested in it anymore nzd CAD for now
set and forget we are currently up
nothing we're actually down
$4,000 so stay tuned and keep in mind
this sucks I don't want to be up right
now but you know we got to do what we
got to do I I'm telling you when I
complete the challenge and I look back
at all these recordings I'm going to be
like damn
that [__] sucked but you know what it
was worth it you set an example for
everybody in the training na you set an
example for people just around the world
that you can really become a millionaire
off just $100 with the right skill set
and if I have to be that guy to be the
first one to ever do it if I have to be
that guy to go through these Lonely
Nights if I have to be that guy to go
through this pain I'll do it but best
believe that if I have to go through all
this to get it and you want it as well
so will you don't think that I'm making
this look easy this is not easy I woke
up at 700 in the morning today and I
probably will I'm probably going to do a
22-hour day probably fall asleep at 5:
in the morning wake up again at 7 8:00
in the morning simple
is it me or that thing [__]
move all right I'm going go take a
shower all right so I just did an IG
live right now 2:30 in the morning we
got about and to add it to the whole
Discord bro people are just [__] like
you know he would just go crazy in there
and bro you know I'm I'm glad I have
like a lot of you know guys like you in
there that helped me out and you know
I'm in there the the best that I could
be you know to answer people's questions
and [__] sh but you know I I am going to
add more weekly calls in there um I've
been filtering out like the better
students like like a Jane juice people
like that where I've been uh telling
them like yo you guys down to do like
classes every day and just add more
value so just the chat doesn't [__]
go crazy like that cuz bro it's and it's
good though because bro you saw today
how many people [__] entered this
trade earlier in the morning you know so
it's just you know it's just a matter of
like the cuz the people that that get
anxious and just go crazy are the new
guys right that they just got started
and [__] how long have you been trading
bro I'm going to be honest with you I
recently just got into this cuz I've
I've been I've been the type of guy
where I've you know I had my own company
or I still have my own company and stuff
like that so trading was never really
like the one way for me to get out of it
um like out of like the basic like
day-to-day struggle or the Matrix is
what people call it yeah yeah yeah so
for me it was more of like a like a like
a backup plan almost but I'm really
starting to get into it bro and I stay
up all [__] night bro all the time I
mean yeah that's that's how it is and
then but but what you um like how long
like a month two months three months
like no no no so for in terms of like
with your strategy bro probably within
the last like six months I started very
like like
February March yeah you're still very
very early on dude like you're [__]
just getting started bro so yeah that's
crazy we just finished the live for
about 15 20 minutes and 15,000 people
tuned in to this [__] live the
community is literally crazy bro this is
what I do it for I do this for you
guys um tired 3 hours of
sleep for nothing
[__] dude why is it going so fast dude
look at this why is it going so
fast [__] trade
update we're down about
$166,000 on this
trade [__] man we literally stayed up
for nothing last night so look yesterday
we were literally at this point right
here and we were're waiting for that 1
hour to engulf that 1 hour engulfed we
are pretty much good right and we
literally were we were good up until
about 3: 4 in the morning that then the
price decided to then started having a
pullback this trade if I would have
opened my eyes at 5: in the morning and
seen this right here I would have bet my
house that this would have been down
here obviously we're wrong why because
you can see how the structure rejected
this level of support and resistance and
then we went bearish you how we broke
under that higher low so now this time
frame went bearish I would have never
expected I would have okay fine the pool
pull back but if this body Candlestick
closes above in the next 11
minutes we're
[__] we're [__] so what I'm going to
be is very strategic and I can predict
these Market moves because I've seen
this a million times so what I'm going
to do is if I see this body holy [__]
man stop it stop it right
now [__] man [__] bro relax chill
chill what's going on dude we were
friends
chill relax there's no way all right so
I'm going to make a decision in the next
8 minutes see what the [__] I'm going to
do with this USD JPY we never decided to
pull back into this area of Interest how
we wanted it to simply just waiting for
it to get to that
point gbpnzd we did that's so funny did
the position we're dra down and then
this position we literally predict the
entry like look look how precise that is
it does not get any more perfect or any
more precise than having a pull back
right to the area boom I obviously
wasn't interested in it because I am in
nzd CAD so for now just set and forget
GBP JPY never made it back to the area
of Interest GBP USD not
interested just holy [__] dude
so this Thursday New York session we
probably
have dude I don't know when I look at it
on the weekly time frame I love this for
the weekly time frame I really do right
so on the weekly time frame I look at it
like this and I can see this Candlestick
closing like that this week I agree I
agree and what I could see is then the
next week filling that chill relax dude
do it slow man don't do it so fast all
right so we're going to wait the next
four or five minutes and then see what
happens so sucks that don't forget I
don't even know why I'm laughing at this
point we do the account boys the
44,000 [__] bro this is why we can't
[__] around talking [__] we [__]
jinxed it talking [__] so we just
took a unnecessarily $40,000 loss on an
ndd cab so look at this right here we
had our stop loss originally set up at
this level right here our stop loss was
very strategically set right above this
1 hour lower high level right here let
me take off all these junk lines that I
have set up right here let me take this
off remove this one and we had this stop
loss set here for a very specific reason
if price hits that point we are
completely wrong we want nothing to do
with the trade right that is what a stop
loss is meant to do but when this body
Candlestick closed I or as it was
getting closing I'm like you know what
it's a very very tight stop loss it's
above this structure level maybe it can
Wick up to this level so what did I
do I moved my stop loss so that stop
loss was here I decided to then you know
what bucket price can actually make it
up to the top of this Wick let me just
move it up it can't it can't it like
price can't hit that point right there
just can't it's it's
possible well then price kept heading to
the upside and I'm actively looking at
this on the 15 minute time frame and the
15-minute time frame I'm looking at all
these little green candlesticks I'm like
okay you know what first dogee it's
going to just create another Wick and
then head to the downside let me just
give it some breathing room from this
point right here cuz as you can see from
this point right here there's literally
about half a pip let me just give it
about an extra six seven Pips so if it
were to hit this high right here with
this price action if it were a wick then
price would head to the downside so now
we have just moved the stop loss for the
second [__]
time and I said you know what that's it
we're gonna cut it at this point and I
broke my trading rule if I would have
just tooken the loss fine cool but I
modified my stop loss I kept moving it
up and up and up just because I was so
invested into the position and I thought
that it was going to go in my favor and
guess what happened paid the [__]
price like an idiot so price clearly
violated my stop loss by completely and
now we were just completely wrong in the
trade whereas if I would have closed out
the position right here with about 20
Pips my loss would have been
$20,000 versus at this point where it's
$40,000 cuz I doubled my stop loss I
went from a 20 pip stop loss to a 40 pip
stop loss where I basically doubled my
risk on the position that I had acquired
for it daily time frame Clos with a
disgusting absolutely disgusting bullish
engulfing Candlestick which truthfully I
am no longer interested in sells this
week on nzdcad so that led us to
have this loss for $44,000 [__] do
and the balance on the account is
$44,000 not on the account so sucks what
a waste because we were actually up
$30,000 and this shows you guys that you
can't
let like your investment into the market
just because I was awake last night up
until 5:00 in the morning watching the
market I went on an IG live with a bunch
of Traders and explain to the trade like
I was just so invested into it I'm like
I can't be wrong I'm Alex G I'm the set
for getet go how could I be wrong well
this is what I needed a humbling moment
to show me that I could be wrong [__]
just [__] happens you don't [__]
you know don't can't predict every move
so lesson learned and not going to
happen again throughout the challenge
I'm so glad I rised a lot less than we
did because that we would have literally
blown the account but this just sets us
back so we're we were last week which
sucks you know so I am out of my word
and
whenever
[__] [__] I had to do that to
the market I'm sorry the market it's
always a [__] Mark it's never my
fault I'm not XG I'm the goat the S
forget goat cuz it's never my fault but
I still have to drive the
beo [__] so funny enough ironically
enough tomorrow I have a jet trip to
Dominican Republic to my tobacco farm I
own a tobacco brand and I got to go make
sure that the guys are making the
tobacco good that the plants are good
the leaves are dry and everything's
being done well and I was planning to go
in either my G wagon or my Bugatti to go
get on my jet to then go to the tobacco
farm so I have to pay 50k now to go to
Dr and a jet and I have to put up on the
beetle so right now we're going to go to
the Hard Rock stadium because we're
going to go film some ads for fan funed
it's the number one Prop Room for sports
betting so you don't have to bet with
your own money anymore you could just
pass a challenge and then they will fund
you to sports bet it's the same thing as
trading and as you know how be how I
became profitable in the trading space
CU I learned how to use risk management
and use other people's money to make
money and then I get a profit spit on it
that's exactly what fan fund it is but
for sports betting so we're going to go
do some ads on it and uh hopefully we
run into some cool people and we're
going to try to potentially run on the
field again you know we're not going to
run on the field we're going to try and
just touch the field we're going to
[Music]
try this looks like this looks like at
the Super
Bowl keep the streak alive
keep streak alive hell yeah y be safe
next time you streaking with us though I
got is that all right this sucks this is
why you want to follow your trading plan
it's kind of ironic we're a $1,000 car
on our way to a $10 million jet how does
that even make sense I guarantee
nobody's done
this so changing shirts waiting for the
guys to pull up for the podcast we're
going to do a podcast right now on our
way to the
[Music]
guys came all the way from London to
L than to meet you my man how are you
pleas we checked out that spot last
night it was fire that
food for how you doing pleas how was the
how was everything yeah great thanks
everyn was fantastic can't wait to go on
this we got a long FL now how you doing
me you guys yeah you oh you guys got REM
too are the best one 100 ft are are
[Music]
we flying everywhere oh [__] and there
no say it's fake it's fake you guys need
here you guys can hit me up all right
all right see travel boys bro good luck
see see you later
[Music]
so fast forward like 10 seconds we're in
our house right here in Dominic which
we'll give you guys a little house tour
after but look check this [__] out we
literally leave our house which you
thought I thought it was going to be a
big house here in the Dominican
Republic and look at our front door
neighbor yeah that's very humbling but
look check how big of the chick like
there's always a bigger boat but I'm
never satisfied never I I never think
it's
enough picture how house picture how big
this house can actually be you look at
it from the side here so he has like an
empty lot to the
side look how far back the actual house
goes so it's not like just a big front
end it's a whole big side of it so right
now trade update we ended off the week
on a $44,000 loss so absolutely sucks we
ended up losing more than we should have
this week
never fails bro
Miami Puerto
Rico and now dominan Republic we just
broke the golf cart like how do we break
a golf cart Cars part
[Music]
two can't break this all right drive
it come on we got it we got it we got it
[Applause]
no no
no all right this one super sick I like
this one but I like more of like the old
school Spanish H oh sh spe
so keep for keep them you got to stand
up so you don't hit your head we have
this one up
here we have one more this
one super super sife look at the look at
the
garage and this you're looking at
boys is your boy alex
G's land right isn't that crazy from
Dunkin Donuts to owning land in a
completely different
country that'd be nice I'm
kidding you can't even buy land in this
actual Community like you could only
rent out because this whole entire
Community is owned by one family it's
probably one of the West neighborhoods
in out of Latin America calleda the
Campo Bad Bunny House houses here V
diesel pretty much everybody so I I just
want to show you guys got a little bit
sidetracked we came here for the weekend
because I own a tobacco brand and I
actually bought into a company that
wasn't a successful
operating tobacco Strand and we bought
into them their marketing was terrible
and we're going to restructure Rebrand
their whole entire marketing so
hopefully some of the tobacco can make
it into this video if not we'll
implement it in the next one but
basically we're going to come see how
the factories see how every single step
of the actual cigar gets made I don't
know if you guys know but there's
425 hand steps in order to make one
single cigar and each single cigar the
one that I own takes 12 years to make so
the actual cigar you're smoking for
their plant to grow for the leaf to cure
for it to dry for it to be the perfect
temperature 12 years so this guy built
that brand for I don't know 20 years ran
it for five he was literally about to
close down we're like you know what
let's buy into it let's bring it back to
life and we bring in marketing and make
it better so we're here having the final
like launch date that we're going to do
of it I'm very excited but you know it's
kind of what I do on my free time when I
am not losing trades on the market and
Argo next week is a turn 10 no Aro ouro
next week on week 10 is oh [__] Are we
going to get run
over that was suck to get
right he went out on a middle of a road
in the medican Republic so next week on
week 10 we're going to try and turn
these
$40,000 back up to
$90,000 every single one of my trades I
share inside of my Discord with my
students where I get on a live call with
them every single Sunday where I give
them the before the during the after if
you guys want to know more about that
just loin loin loin the link below loin
it yeah you've been you've been out of
America for one day you talk English
yeah if you guys aren't part of the S
foret Community you're missing out we're
literally sharing all these trades even
though we did lose this week Go I mean
obviously if you're at this point you
saw the whole video we literally
predicted 80% of the markets this week
we managed to only enter one simply
because we're obviously entering higher
risk trades if I were to be trading my
own personal account I would enter every
single Market because the opportunity is
there but obviously since I'm ring 100%
or almost 100% I have to be very
selective on the actual trade that I'm
doing so on a normal account you can
make money every single week with these
analysis that I'm doing all you have to
do is join the set and forget Community
oh siit poor oh wow look at
GT3 that has by the way this is a third
world country yeah this is a third world
country to see a [__] GT3 is
ridiculous there's Lambos like they
shows you that there's money in all
these different countries they just
lowkey so
if you're not in the set and forget
Community you're missing out see you
guys next week and set and forget